Move on. No, let's not move on. Let's stay right there. Tell me which hospital that Israel has
targeted. Tell me which one. You said Israel targets hospitals. The only hospital that got
targeted so far in this war was targeted by Islamic Jihad. Okay. Okay. Don't tell me about
it. And by the way, it's been proven with certainty, it's been proven with certainty
that the headquarters of Hamas is under the Al-Shifa hospital in Gaza City. Now, you know
what happened a couple of days ago? Mark, are you going to let me finish? I cannot allow you to say
15 things that are unfactual and not be challenged on them. I'm happy to let you talk, but I'm going
to ask clarifying questions. You're going to tell me what's factual? Mark, I spent five years of my
life studying this, living it. What was the last time you were in Gaza, Mark? What was the last
time you were in Gaza? 18 months ago. What was the last time you were in Gaza? A few years ago.
Okay. So you said Al-Shifa hospital. It's been proven Hamas headquarters. What independent
reference, what source, what investigation has proven that? Who has proven that it's an Al-Shifa
hospital since it's been a proven fact? Who proved it? So now we're going to get into this basic,
like, Holocaust denying idea that that evidence that Israel has shown is not valid. I mean,
is that what you're doing? Do you deny that people were raped?
No, no, no. Are you going to deny stuff?
Everybody that challenges you is not doing Holocaust denial. You said that it's a Hamas
headquarter. I simply asked you. I simply asked you for evidence of it. I said, who? And you
immediately equated it to Holocaust denial.
Israel has presented evidence. Ask, ask the CIA. Ask, ask, ask anybody. Ask the CIA, sir.
Yeah. You don't trust, you don't trust the government. You don't trust the American
government. You don't trust the Israeli government. Who should we trust? Hamas? You want to trust
Hamas? Go ahead. Trust Hamas. The people, the people that destroy, that destroy lives day and night.
David, here's the point. Here's the point. Under Article 8 of the Rome Statute and under Article 33 of the
1949 Geneva Convention, international law forbids the targeting of civilians. Do you disagree with
that? I don't disagree with that at all. Okay. Would you agree that targeting a refugee camp
that has children in it and adults who are non-Hamas members, who are not actors in the military,
would constitute targeting a civilian? I completely disagree with that.
I completely disagree. If Israel is targeting Hamas in a refugee camp and it's pinpointing its
attacks on Hamas and there is collateral damage, there's collateral damage. That's war. That's
called war. W-A-R. That's what it is. So here's the challenge, David. Israel argues that Hamas is
everywhere in Gaza, that they're under every hospital, that they're in every university, that they're in
every refugee camp. You agree with that, right? We can agree to that. No, Israel does not think
they're everywhere. Israel thinks that they are where they are. And those are in many but not all
civilian locations. So the challenge is, by that logic, virtually every civilian location
is vulnerable and viewed as a legitimate target. And so what happens is thousands of innocent people
die. Again, when you bomb a refugee camp, there's no reason to believe that it's the only way to get
at a Hamas target. When a hospital is bombed, there's no reason to believe that's the only way
to do this. And if you know that the, quote unquote, collateral damage, as you call it,
is thousands of civilians, then yes, it seems like an improper thing. But again, it's not just me
saying this. The UN, the International Red Cross, all of these bodies, including outside of the UN,
who you said you don't respect, they also agree that these are war crimes. So why does the entire
international community believe that these are war crimes and not you? So, because I think I have
an unbiased view, and I think there's a lot of anti-Semitism in the world. Okay, there's a lot
of anti-Israel behavior in the world. But let me ask you a question, Mark. Israel gets...